{
    "subject": "Elissa_Ambrose",
    "predicate": "hasChild",
    "object": "Sarah_Mlynowski",
    "human_readable": "Elissa Ambrose has a child named Sarah Mlynowski.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988528311252594,
            "question": "Does Sarah Mlynowski have a parent named Elissa Ambrose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9862254858016968,
            "question": "Is Sarah Mlynowski a biological child of Elissa Ambrose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.984632134437561,
            "question": "Is Sarah Mlynowski related to Elissa Ambrose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9771271347999573,
            "question": "Who has a child named Sarah Mlynowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9444963932037354,
            "question": "Name the child of Elissa Ambrose."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8981000185012817,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Elissa Ambrose and Sarah Mlynowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8651025891304016,
            "question": "What is the name of Elissa Ambrose's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8630850911140442,
            "question": "If you were to create a family tree, where would Elissa Ambrose and Sarah Mlynowski be placed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7829180359840393,
            "question": "Who is the mother of Sarah Mlynowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7354477643966675,
            "question": "What is the name of Elissa Ambrose's daughter?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elissa Ambrose has a child named Sarah Mlynowski.",
            "html": "yago_12909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the mother of Sarah Mlynowski?",
            "html": "yago_12909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to create a family tree, where would Elissa Ambrose and Sarah Mlynowski be placed?",
            "html": "yago_12909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Elissa Ambrose's child?",
            "html": "yago_12909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12909_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Elissa Ambrose has a child named Sarah Mlynowski.\" Each document mentions Sarah Mlynowski as the daughter of Elissa Ambrose."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}